tvsa.co.za 2017-10-07

# Privacy Policy | TVSA

TVSA respects your right to privacy and has fully secured database systems in place to collect and manage all personal information gathered in operating its services.

Our privacy policy is as follows:

**Becoming a member of TVSA**

Every area of TVSA (except TVSA Central - our Members Only section) can be browsed without you submitting any personal information.

To access certain of TVSA's services you will need to become a TVSA member which means you will need to submit a valid email adress. These services include, but are not limited to: becoming a full member of TVSA, creating blogs, posting replies, signing up for newsletters, submitting contact forms and entering competitions.

Your email adress may be used by TVSA to make contact with you in instances where we need to provide you with TVSA-related information. TVSA gaurantees the confidentiality of your e-mail address. In no instances will your e-mail address be given, sold or rented to third parties.

Any additional personal information you submit (name, address, telephone number, etc.) is voluntary.

In the future, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In this instance, we may include your information among the transferred assets.

TVSA displays links to external websites and cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies nor content of any of the sites accessed via one of these links.

TVSA cannot be held responsible for a breach of privacy in instances where users share their personal information with any other user on the site.

TVSA may disclose your details to a third party only in instances where it is required to by law or in instances where it does so in good faith to act to protect the interests of the site, its members or others.

**Information collected by us using technology**

We use various internet technologies to manage TVSA and track the use of our services. Non-personal information that we collect using these technologies may be combined with other information about you.

**Device information.** We may collect non-personal information about the computer, mobile device or other device you use to access TVSA services, such as IP address, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser type and browser language.

**Cookies and other similar technologies.** We use "cookies," tags, scripts, and other similar technologies which allow us to manage access to and use of our services.

They allow us to recognise you, understand how you use the site and provide you with a personalised experience of the site.

**Analytics, log files and reading history**

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses (the region or general location where your computer or device is accessing the Internet), browser type, operating system and other usage information about the use of TVSA, including a history of the pages you view.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve the services we offer you, including customized recommendations, advertising and to track access and use of the TVSA Services across  devices.

**Third Parties**

Some of the advertisements on TVSA are delivered or served by third-party companies which may collect information about your use of  TVSA.

These companies may place or recognise cookies or other technology to track certain non-personal information about our website users.

For example, we use Google to serve advertisements onto the TVSA website, which use the Google Doubleclick cookie, and in some cases, a unique device identifier, to show you ads based on your visit to TVSA and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the Google Doubleclick cookie by visiting [the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences).

In the course of serving certain advertisements, an advertiser may place or recognise a unique cookie on your browser in order to collect certain information about your use of TVSA.

For example, an advertiser or ad server may be able to collect your device’s unique identifier in the course of serving an ad. In many cases, this information could be used to show you ads on other websites based on your interests.

We do not have access to, nor control over, these third parties' use of cookies or other tracking technologies or how they may be used.

The list of third parties that may be using cookies to serve advertising on our website are:

**Admarula** (<http://www.admarula.com/>)

**Google** (<https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated?hl=en>)

For more information about this, or to learn your choices about not having this non-personal information used to target ads to you, please [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

You can opt out of personalised Google advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

You can also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

Your access to our website should not be affected if you do not accept cookies served by third parties.

**User generated content and public activities (including comments, reviews and blog posts)**

TVSA offers opportunities to engage in public activities. "Public activities" are any actions you take on the website that are designed to be visible to other users, including comments, show and actor reviews, ratings, blog posts or any other items that you submit.

Any information you disclose in your public activities, along with your screen name or ID, or any image or photo, becomes public and may be used by TVSA for online and offline promotional or commercial uses in any and all media.

If you choose to engage in public activities, you should be aware that any personal information you submit publicly can be read, collected and used by other users.

We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in the course of your public activities and we have no responsibility to publish, take down, remove or edit any of your public activities or submissions.

Public activities may be included in our RSS feeds and other distribution formats. As a result, your public activities may appear on other websites, blogs, or feeds. We are not responsible for any personal information you choose to make public via your public activities. Sharing will be deemed to have been done by you, not TVSA.

When you share or recommend links to content on a third-party platform (such as Facebook, Google+ and Twitter), that action and any information you share will be covered by their privacy policy.

**Use of your information**

This is what we use your information for:

**Provide the services you request**

We use the information we gather about you to enable your use of TVSA and to fulfill your requests for certain information and services, such as your participation in blog creation and posts, reviews, messages on the message boards and e-mail newsletters (if you’ve subscribed to these).

**Statistical analysis**

We perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users of TVSA, and their subscribing and purchasing patterns, for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base. We use this information for analysis purposes to improve your experience of TVSA and the marketing you receive on the site.

**Customising your experience**

We use the information that we collect to allow advertising to be targeted to the users for whom such advertising is most pertinent. We also use this information to customise certain features of TVSA to provide you with an enhanced experienced based on the type of device you are using to access the site.

**Relevant Advertising**

We may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on TVSA to be targeted to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer's experience and the effectiveness of the ads. We disclose information to third parties only in aggregate or de-identified form.

**The protection of your information**

To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place commercially reasonable physical, technical and administrative controls to protect the information. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.
